ACHIEVEMENTS
HELP
LEADERBOARDS
UNLOCK FULL GAME
TIKI TEMPLE
Other Destinations
Start New Game
OFF
ON
Ribbit!
Options
Click to Enter
Revisit Past Zones
CONTINUE!
CONTINUE GAME
Paused
Try Again!
ADVENTURE
CHALLENGE
High Scores:
MAIN MENU
Victory!
Success!
Continue game from last checkpoint?
Tap to continue…
BONUS
Zuma's Revenge!
Start a new game from…
…any unlocked zone!
More Games
Final Stats
Time:
Score:
Final Score:
TAP TO BATTLE
MAGA MAGA
The shaman controlled two slave tikis who guarded him day and night. So long as they stood,nothing colud harm him.
TAP TO BATTLE
KOLO KAMARI
The vermin of the insect god drained the blood and life of their prey.Only a great blast of fire and noise could drive the demon away.
TAP TO BATTLE
BARON DIGO
No arrow could pierce his stony hide,yet wicked baron digo cut up his soul and hid it in the ribcages of his victims.
TAP TO BATTLE
CEPHALO KA
The inky darkness and shields of power hide the monster's secret weakness... His soft and fleshy underside.
TAP TO BATTLE
Kahtiki Khan
Elders tell of a lost city in the jungle,where a stone demon takes the heads of men.None who go ever return.
TAP TO BATTLE
ZHAKA MU
Ultimate devil spirit
This is the sanctum of evil.But only in darkness will the final demon reveal himself.
Congratulations!
Conitnue
You have discovered the secret of Tiki Island!
Buy Full Game
Gamertag
Do you want to interrupt your music and use game background music?
Error communicating with Xbox LIVE
Title Update Available
Update Game to communicate with Xbox LIVE
An update is available! This update is required to connect to Xbox LIVE. Update now?
There was an error uploading your score. Please check your network connection and try again.
Complete the Challenge Mode
Win a Challenge Level
Beat a regular rail level without moving the frog
Build your score multiplier up to 5X
Shoot 15 balls and make 15 matches... in a row!
Make a match by shooting a ball through a gap in the curve
Defeat Zhaka Mu and discover the secret of the island!
Just win a regular level. Easy hu?!
Defeat Cephalo Ka and his Inky Ink Attack
Defeat Kolo Kamari and his Swarm of Bugs
Defeat Baron Digo and his Skeleton Crew
Defeat Maga Maga and his Tiki Minions
Defeat the Cluttonous Kahtiki Khan
Beat a lily pad level without jumping lily pads
Fe Frog
Challenge Accepted
Frozen Frog
Power Player
C-C-C-C-Chain Bonus!
Thread the Needle
Time for Tadpoles!
You Win!
Cephalopod Smashe
Pestilence Pacifier
Bone Picker
Tiki Trampler
Jaw Breaker
Frog Statue
Unlock Achievement: 
Achievements
G
BONUS! +$1
10 SECONDS!
 MULTIPLIER ACTIVE!
New High Score!
CURVE CLEARED
COMBO 
QUAD GAP BONUS!!!!
TRIPLE GAP BONUS!!!
DOUBLE GAP BONUS!!
GAP BONUS!
CHAIN BONUS
Well, that didn't go quite like I planned.
But I'm a bad loser. And I have one more trick.
Just one more stage!
Let's watch some special effects!
Wheeeeeeee!
Strange Frog, why do you intrude on us?
This island is no holiday resort!
Five fierce chiefs guard our mysteries!
Time:
Score:
Iron Frog $1 - $2
Level $1 - $2
Time Elapsed:
Ace Time:
Deaths This Level:
Lives Remaining:
Challenge Target:
Ace Target:
Lives Replenished!
CHALLENGE!
Score $1 points
TIME!
MULTIPLIER BONUS: +$1%%
+$1 points
You didn't clear any levels.
You cleared $1 of 10 levels.
Final Score: $1 
A new high score!
Your Best Score: None
Your Best Score: $1
level
SO YOU HAVE UNCOVERED MY TRUE FORM.
TREMBLE, MORTAL, AND NOW BURN!
New best time!
New high score!
Level Aced!
Challenge: $1  Ace: $2  
Level Complete!
Points This Level
Total Points
Perfect Level Bonus
Max Combo\nMax Chain\nGap Shots\nFruit
Ace Time\nYour Time\nBonus\nBest
Tap to continue
BERZERK!
THE BOSS IS GROWING IMPATIENT!
Who are you,\ntasty frog?
Roar! I'm famished!
Trespassers will\nbe eaten!
Dare you approach?
Getting closer!
I'm readying for you!
Frog soup, I love it for sure!
No skill can cheat your death!
Almost suppertime!
At last! Let's eat!
They call me\nMaga Maga!
I'm a Witch Doctor, y'know!
I've got loads of magic on me!
My slave tikis will deal big pain!
My spells will\nblind you!
My magic is pure evil!
'Maga Maga' is short for 'Mashed Enemy'!
Do you feel it?\nThe terror?
Are you brave enough?
Time for\nsorcerous judgment!
They call me\nBaron Digo!
All who smell the Baron know fear!
I'll have your\nsoul, Frog!
Baron Digo is\nsuper wicked!
I'm immune to balls!
Run now while\nyou can!
What? You still come?
Has nobody told you my name?
To repeat: I am\nBaron Digo!
Baron Digo is the name of your DOOM!
Bzzzzzzz! Bzt!
Say, how do you like pestilence?
What's your take\non bugs?
How do you like wasps?
Bee stings:\ngreat or fantastic?
I'm an insect god,\nby the by!
Insects follow\nmy advice!
So glad you're coming my way!
You are tough but not enough, Frog!
Now my tiny friends will FEED!
ARRRG! I'm so angry!
Now I'm even\nangrier!
I'm calm now, but only for a second.
Pow! Even angrier than I was!
Can you face my rage?
Your approach\ninsults me, Frog!
I'm not afraid of you!
I feel the anger welling up again!
I can't take much more waiting!
Let's begin our\nfurious battle!
Five champions have you defeated.
Five chiefs you have humbled.
Yet still you are\nnot satisfied.
Still you seek\nour summit.
This island is\nonly doom.
Your road is only pain.
I wear the\nmysterious mask.
I wear the\nmysterious robe.
We will never give up our mysteries.
Now we see how a frog DIES!
Roar! You're back!
Growl! This time\nI'm ready!
I'm going to\ndodge all over!
You won't lay a\nball on me!
Much harder\nnow, right?
Feeling the\npressure yet?
No way you're a hero!
You're not good enough for this mode!
I gnash my teeth\nin anticipation!
Rematch!
Kahtiki says you\nhave improved!
I'm hardly worried!
My Witch magic is hula strong now!
My tikis have been training hard!
My slave: You\nwill be it!
Float like an ooga, sting like a booga!
I've been monitoring my diet!
I practically live\nat the gym!
My witch muscles\nare huge!
Ding ding!\nLet's go!
I'm still Baron Digo!
Yep! Baron Digo.\nThat's my name.
For a while I forgot who I was.
Your beating induced amnesia in me.
I wandered nameless for a time.
I checked my\nmail and remembered:\nBaron Digo
Now I've got more confidence than ever!
No arrow will pierce my hide!
Baron Digo delivers 24-hour DOOM!
Face your enemy:\nme, Baron Digo!
Well, well, well. . .\nIf it isn't the Frog.
I know you, Frog.\nAll too well!
So, you up for another shot?
Can you beat my\nflies a second time?
Trust me, buddy,\nthere's no way!
Seriously, frog.\nYou're done.
I've got lots more insects this time!
Are you ready for moths and ants?
My insects are the knees of bees!
Back away, frog!\nJust back away!
I know you, Frog.\nYou defeated me.
I was angry before. Now I'm cold.
My steely disposition is my new shield.
I am unflappable.
I am calm like a lake.
Nothing makes\nme angry.
I see now that my rage defeated me.
My new serenity\nwill be your end.
Wait! I lost my\nkeys! ARRRG!
I'm incredibly mad\nabout my keys!
Welcome back, Frog!
Wow, you're great\nat this mode!
Even I can't\nget this far!
I've never seen\nball-spitting like\nyours!
Can't resist the challenge, huh?
Frog, I name thee 'Hero of Modes!'
I'm Zhaka Mu,\nby the way.
I've got a whole new\nmystery for you!
Go for the gold! You're almost there!
So close to the\nfinal mystery!
You broke my mouth!
My tongue's hanging out all like glahhhh.
My four brothers will avenge my tongue!
Ooga! With a helping of booga sauce!
My slave tikis completely flopped on the job.
Where did all my magic go?
You beat me so hard I forgot my own name!
And I was really attached to it, too!
Some day, some way, I'll make you pay!
I threw every insect in the book at you!
But you exploded me in no time flat!
Beat it, Frog! Go swimming, why don't you?
My arm! It's broken! And it doesn't even have bones!
I really let myself down. Next time I'll be angrier.
Oh, well, have fun dying on the volcano!
You have won, so I reveal one final truth.
You have long thought yourself alone.
But... you are not the last of your kind.
Coconuts! Shattered! Beyond repair!
My tongue's doing no better than the first time!
You really know your balls!
My witchy magic failed me with big aplomb!
I can't even blame my slave tikis this time.
I should've been a lawyer.
What's this? Again you defeat me?
I don't deserve to call myself Baron Digo.
What's that, Pookie? You still believe in me? Yay! 
Well, there it was.
I talked a big game and left the same holes in my defense.
Am I ever going to learn, even a little bit?
Oh, foof! Why does this keep happening?
My guru said I needed to chill but it didn't help.
I guess this is pretty much your island now.
Wow. Just wow. I've played a lot of Zuma.
But you stomped all over me in every way.
Try the Iron Frog mode or the Challenges!
'Cuz this mode is FINISHED!
Do you think to best me so easily? Minions, come hither!
Try and breach my defences!
As long as my shield stands, you shall fail!
I hunger for plenty!
You will make a fine meal!
I bet you're good and crunchy!
What goes well with toasted frog?
I'll bake you in a frog pot pie!
Nothing can harm me!
I cannot be beaten!\nI'm unbeatable!
See how strong my magics are?
I went to the best voodoo school!
Step it up, slave tikis! What do I pay you for?
Whoop! Skeleton warriors attack!
Baron Digo delivers the damage!
I am Baron of Digo!
Baron Digo rules with skeletons!
Who's the Baron?\nMe! I am!
I'm grinnin' like crazy!
Bite, my pretties, bite!
It's all about the stinging!
Confuse him, my tiny buddies!
I love the sound of insects in the morning!
I'm overly bitter!
I'm annoyed!
I'm affronted!
I'm irritable!
You nettle me!
You infuriate me!
Consider me maddened!
Stern I am, and stone!
I have no heart to care!
This frown means death!
I am a rock,\nI am this island.
I am the totem of despair!
I crush you!
You sully our island!
The blood of the volcano awaits!
No living thing can survive!
Your soul shall be forfeit!
Your puny spheres cannot stop me!
Give up this  time, frog!
No way you beat me twice!
I lull you into false confidence!
My teeth are feeling gnashy!
My magic is stronger now!
I've been taking magic night classes!
Bah!
Sorcerous power is ready to defeat you!
Stop hitting me, frog!
Ha! The Baron deals defeat!
The Baron fears no hero frog
In case you forgot, I'm Baron Digo!
Digo's the name, pain's the game!
Make way for magnificent me!
Insects are the dominant lifeform!
We owe everything to bees and ants!
I'm fully pestilent!
Six legs good, four legs bad!
Amphibians are our enemies!
My rage is like ice.
Nothing can make me lose my cool.
Your insult only hardens my resolve.
LOSING IT! RRAARRRRG!!!
I am master of my temper.
Keep it up, Frog!
You're doing great!
Match those crazy orbs!
Almost time for my devil form!
I love watching a master at work!
I'm constantly amazed!
How do you do it?
You should write a strategy guide!
Your Zuma moves inspire me! 
This Devil costume's pretty scary, huh?
No! You are much too powerful!
Even my doomy chicken legs were useless.
I yield to your amphibian agility!
Oof! Got me! Well, I gotta run.
Catch you later! Enjoy the fake credits!
Baaawwwk! I am Zhaka Mu! Fear me!
You'll need something more explosive to hurt me!
MY SHIELD BREACHED! UNTHINKABLE!
Bah, hit me frog! Next time it shall not be this easy!
Maybe that wasn't my true face.
I have an even truer one!
You cannot defeat the truest face of Zhaka Mu!
Actually, this never was my true face.
I was just trying out my Hallowe'en costume
Let's dance one more time!
LITTLE FROG HAS CALLED DOWN THE TIGER!
NOW HE WILL REAP THE PAIN! RAAAAAAAR!
I will munch your power and add it to mine!
Do you have fight in you? Shoot me if you dare!
You dared! How dare you?
BRING FORTH THE BALLS!
Fiesty meal! Break through the wall and hit me again!
Puny frog! Your weakness is of legends!
What foolishness to think you can hurt me!
Let us test your mettle. SHOOT ME IF YOU DARE!
HOW TO PLAY
Fill
BONUS BAR
to earn
BONUS BALLS.
Bonus Balls
MULTIPLY POINTS
earned!
Good luck, you have only
3 MINUTES.
Bonus Bar
Challenge Score:
Ace Score:
Your Best:
Difficulty:
Beat level  $1 in Adventure Mode\nto unlock this cup.
Beat an available challenge\nto unlock more levels.
Select A Zone
Beat this zone in Adventure Mode to unlock this cup.
Reach this level in Iron Frog Gauntlet to play.
Beat an available challenge to unlock more levels.
Beat all previous challenges to unlock this cup.
Choose a level.
Checkpoint Reached!
( Tap to continue! )
If you lose all your lives, you can restart from this level!
(Tap and hold to fast forward)
Spooky, no? It's like a dark mirror.
Something like that. Either way,
how can you defeat... yourself?
This evil frog version looks pretty cool, huh?
Maybe he should be the star of Revenge of Zuma's Revenge!
Anyway, en garde!
Try Again!
Lives Replenished!
$1 Lives Left
1 Life Left
Yes
No
ARE YOU SURE?
Challenge mode games are\nNOT SAVED!\nEnd this game anyway?
Iron Frog mode games are\nNOT SAVED!\nEnd this game anyway?
Your progress will be saved.\nDo you wish to end your game?
Are you sure?\nA restart from here\nwill set your score to zero.
Are you sure you wish to quit?\nThis will make the mighty Zuma angry!
CANCEL
Play
Back To Menu
Replay
Cancel
Foolish frog! He was not Zhaka Mu!
You only battled my chef!
Now gaze upon the true face of Zhaka Mu!
I must say you are the Zuma-est Champion.
These levels are really really hard.
But you've almost finished Heroic Mode!
BOMB
REWIND
SLOWDOWN
LIGHTNING
TRI-SHOT
LASER
POISONED!
SLOOOOOOW-MO!
HELP
Destroys nearby balls in its fiery wake.
Rolls the balls backwards.
Slows ball speed for a short period of time.
Destroys every ball of the target color.
Fires 3 balls at once.
Zaps balls with pinpoint accuracy.
License Agreement
Privacy Policy
Terms Of Service
OK
LEGAL
version 
Visit Website?
Minimize Zuma's Revenge! and go to external website?
If you no longer wish to send anonymous game play information to PopCap, slide the box and we will disable the transmission of such information.
User Sharing
Tremble, frog!
You face Zhaka Mu!
Prepare to witness my true form!
Hey, Frog, it's me again!
I'm the chicken guy pretending to be Zhaka Mu!
Way too bright!
In darkness I await.
Kill those torches!
Extinguish the torches!
Shipwrecked!
Castaway
Echo Beach
Bones of an Idol
Switchback Slider
Jungle Clearing
Sand Trap
Nasal Passage
Creeper Copse
Darkness Falls
Kahtiki Khan
Watering Hole
Overgrown Plaza
Lilypad Leap
Sandspirals
Abandoned Well
Face Your Fear
Seven Sides (minus one)
Vines of Vengeance
Logroller
The Horseshoe
Maga Maga
Ancient Cistern
Blossom Grove
Empty Cistern
Ancestral Tongue
Mossy Square
Mosaic Mayhem
Strange Smile
Lichen Lair
Ghosts of the Past
Double Danger
Baron Digo
Swamp Spin
Deadmarsh
Stagnant Ponds
Brackish Pool
Justified and Ancient
Ancient Inlay
Secret Circle
Moai Slide
Tide Pools
Skull Coral
Kolo Kamari
Coral Catch
Wave Babies
Submergathon
Anglers Cove
Coelacanth Cave
Ocean Floor
Smuggler's Depth
Pacific Divide
The Deep
Shark Den
Cephalo Ka
Flowing Tiki Rage
Subterran Solaris
Reflection in Magma
Obsidian Isle
Underworld Remnants
Thermal Vortex
Molten Dais
Basaltic Approach
Searing Visage
Descent into Anguish
Torchlit Sanctum
Ultimate Boss Zhaka Mu
His Crumbliness
Shadow Frog
Serpent Stare
Fungal Fatality
Lot's Wife
Future Fuels
Fossil Food
What is that thing?
Creeper Creeps
Web Two Point Oh
As The Worm Turns
Chew Your Food
Seven Sides
Smugglers Depth
Drumstick Willie
Loading
Passing time while game loads...
Thinking about cheese...
Hungering for gap bonuses...
Calculating parallaxes...
Bobbing back and forth...
Considering strategy...
Expecting storm clouds to pass...
Feeling upbeat about chances...
Feeling kinda seasick...
Smiling happily...
Squaring circles...
Shuttling electrons...
Loving being a frog...
Staying confident...
Being green...
Steeling self for challenge...
Anticipating fun...
Updating loading bar...
Effecting particles...
Wishing for a pony...
Dreaming of greatness...
Saying "Ribbit"
Floating points...
Reading readmes...
Sizing up the situation...
Hoping for lots of powerups...
Reviewing tiki knowledge...
Burping uncontrollably...
Sharpening senses...
Riding waves...
Regretting abandoning ship...
Getting teensy bit worried...
Kill curve completely for large curve clear bonus.
Break balls behind gaps for gap shot bonus.
Shoot tasty fruit for delicious fruit bonus.
Make many matches with one shot for combo bonus.
Halt fast curves with many small combos.
Knock balls far back with great combo.
Make match after match for ever growing chain bonus.
Chains win early, but a masterful frog learns all tricks.
Risk much in gap shots.  A smaller gap earns many more points.
A wise frog has eyes open always for powerups.
Use powerups to collect fruit blocked by balls.
Bomb powerup destroys nearby balls.
Rollout moves too fast?  Seek slow powerup.
Rewind powerup pulls balls back for short time.
Laser powerup can break any ball, but powerup ball best.
Four shots only you have with the laser powerup.
Laser powerup slows curve when active.
Tri-shot powerup destroys great swath of balls.
Lightning powerup breaks all balls of one color.
Do not want laser?  Tap frog to swiftly deactivate.
Current color no good?  Tap the frog to swap.
For great precision, tap down and drag to aim carefully.
Earnest frog!  Welcome is yet your return!
Again once you return, eager frog!
Welcome back, frog of great mastery!
It is very dangerous to run with a stick.
UFOs avoid this island for reasons!
They say the balls roll always!
I find this breeze pleasingly cool.
The meaning of Zuma is highly mysterious!
Once you get to know him, the Golden Skull is not so bad.
Where do balls come from? Where do they go?
I enjoy red balls best. No, wait... green!
We have not enough sand on this island.
The volcano is acting up again...
Tiki Bosses like to assert themselves!
Courage goes a long way on Tiki Island.
I need to get more surfing in.
My nose begins now to itch!
He who lights the torches carries the flame.
I have been holding this for a looooooong time.
My hat carries golden idol of greatness.
Solid frog, dare you do battle once more?
Sometimes yearn I for nice comfy desk job.
Sun sets over angry island. Let's party with balls!
Welcome to Zuma's Revenge!
Welcome back, $1!
Tap to enter
Jungle of Mystery
Unlocked!
LOCKED!
Oh no! Jungle Boss is on a rampage! Blast him through holes in the curve when his shield is down. But don't let the curve reach the skull!
You've awakened Village Boss from his slumber! Use the lilypads to take shots at his heads when they glow. Be sure to keep the balls out of the skull!
Oh no! Jungle Boss is on a rampage! Blast him through holes in the curve when his shield is down. But don't let the curve reach the skull!
You've awakened Village Boss from his slumber! Use the lilypads to take shots at his heads when they glow. Be sure to keep the balls out of the skull!
Score:
Lives:
(Ace: $1)
Music Volume
Sound Effects
Help
OK
Main Menu
Credits
Legal
Time:
Colorblind Assist
Keep Going!
Music Volume (off)
Level
Level $1\nChallenge:\n$2\nAce:\n$3
Bonus Ball Points: $1   Best Bonus:  $2
You didn't beat the Challenge Score
You beat the Challenge Score!
You beat the Ace Score!
Challenge Mode Unlocked!
New Challenge Zone Unlocked!
Dazed!
Point Target Reached!
Ace Target Reached!
Next Level Tip:
Tikis return! Protect me!
PROXIMITY BOMB
Bomb
SLOW
Slow
ACCURACY
Accuracy
REVERSE
Reverse
TRI-SHOT
Tri-Shot
LIGHTNING
Lightning
LASER
Laser
BONUS BALL
Bonus Ball
Franzi
Sophia
Tanya
Shawn
Chad
Rick
Liv
John
Jeff
Ben
Sukhbir
Jason
Brian
Tysen
Returning to Menu
The Reverse powerup\nrolls the balls in the\nopposite direction.
The Slowdown powerup\nreduces the speed of\nballs on the curve.
The Accuracy powerup\nmakes your shots faster\nand easier to target.
The Tri-shot fires three\ndestructive balls of doom!
The Lightning powerup\ndestroys all balls of\nyour target's color.
The Laser zaps balls\nand fruit with\npinpoint accuracy.
Use the right mouse button to\ncancel the Laser powerup.
When changing lily pads try\nusing the right mouse button.
Use the right mouse button to\nswap between ball colors.
You can jump to an empty lily pad\nby tapping on it.
Use the Laser powerup to trigger\nother powerups!
Shoot fruit for extra points\nand a Zuma bar boost.
Shooting through gaps increases\nthe points you get for a match!
Beating a level without dying\nwill earn a Perfect Level Bonus.
Beating Ace Time on a level will\ngive you a bonus.
The Laser powerup slows time so\nyou can make precise shots.
The Laser powerup can be used to\ncollect fruit!
Fill the Zuma bar to stop new\nballs from coming.
The Accuracy powerup makes your\nshots faster for a short period.
You receive a Chain Bonus for\neach consecutive match after\nfive in a row.
Get multiple matches in a single\nshot for a Combo Bonus.
Beat Adventure mode to unlock\nother modes!
Once you've beaten a zone,\ntry it again in Challenge mode!
Use the right mouse button to\ncancel the Laser powerup.
When changing lily pads try\nusing the right mouse button.
Use the right mouse button to\nswap between ball colors.
You can jump to an empty lilypad\nby clicking on it.
Use the Laser powerup to trigger\nother powerups!
Shoot fruit for extra points\nand a Zuma bar boost.
Shooting through gaps increases\nthe points you get for a match!
The Lightning powerup\ndestroys all balls of\nyour target's color.
Beating a level without\nlosing a life will earn a\nPerfect Level Bonus.
Beating Ace Time on a level will\ngive you a bonus.
The Laser powerup slows time so\nyou can make precise shots.
The Laser powerup can be used to\ncollect fruit!
Fill the Zuma bar to stop new\nballs from coming.
The Accuracy powerup makes your\nshots faster for a short period.
You receive a Chain Bonus for\neach consecutive match after\nfive in a row.
Get multiple matches in a single\nshot for a Combo Bonus.
HEROIC FROG
ADVENTURE
Highest Level Reached
Best Adventure Time
Best Adventure Score
None
Levels Aced
Number of Deaths
Perfect Levels
Clear Curve Bonuses
Deadliest Boss
Deadliest Curve
Boss $1 (Died $2x)
$1 (Died $2x)
Total Time Played
TIKI TEMPLE
CHALLENGE
Highest Score
Challenge Scores Achieved
Ace Scores Achieved
Stone Coins Earned
Gold Coins Earned
Highest Multiplier Bonus
Favorite Curve
$1 (Played $2x)
IRON FROG
Number of Attempts
Number of Victories
Best Time
Best Score
Highest Level
Greatest Nemesis
Level $1 (Died $2x)
Total Time Played
STATS
Longest Chain
Largest Combo
Largest Gap Score
Gap Shots
Double Gap Shots
Triple Gap Shots
Fruits Collected
Bombs Detonated
Lasers Landed
Lightning Unleashed
Tri-Shots Tripped
MORE STATS
Balls Swapped
Balls Fired
Favorite Powerup
Combo Bonus Points
Chain Bonus Points
Gap Shot Points
Powerup Points
Total Time Played
Fruit Bombed
Balls Discarded
Deaths After Zuma
Tap Here to Fire!
Match ^dfa925^3 or more^oldclr^ balls of the same color!
Fill the ^dfa925^Zuma Bar^oldclr^ to stop new balls rolling out.\n\n^49d63a^TAP TO PLAY!
Don't let the balls reach the skull pit!
Tap here to jump!
Tap the frog to swap balls!
Shoot ^dfa925^fruit^oldclr^ to fill the Zuma bar even faster!\n\n^49d63a^SHOOT THE FRUIT!
A New Version Update Available
Hey young frog!\n You just reached the end of this Trial version.\n Do you want to buy the full game \n to continue your adventures?
Unlock full game to continue Zuma's adventures !!!
Unlock full game to continue Zuma's adventures ?
Unlock Zuma's Revenge?
Buy Zuma's Revenge to unlock this feature?
Tip:
Unlock Challenge Mode by\ndefeating level 10 in Adventure Mode.
Jungle of Mystery
Quiet Village
Lost City
Mosquito Coast
Underwater Grotto
Volcano Temple
Mettle of the Monkey
Rooster Rumble
Jackal Jam
Marsh Madness
Undersea Undertaking
Serpent Scuffle
Peacock's Provocation
Easy
Medium
Extra Medium
Hard
Very Hard
Seriously Hard
INSANE
LEADERBOARDS
ACHIEVEMENTS
By purchasing and/or using this application, you agree to the terms of the End User License Agreement and EA's Privacy Policy and Terms of Service.\nCertain Wi-Fi security settings will allow you to connect but not use the application's network features, including Leaderboards. Network fees may apply.\n\n© 2012 Electronic Arts Inc. PopCap, PopCap logo, EA, EA logo and Zuma's Revenge are trademarks of Electronic Arts Inc.\nCustomer service: Send email to help%eamobile.com
About
pts
